Friends, whenever you get your bike insured,
then get it insured from a good company only
because friends, what
happens is that whenever your
bike meets with an accident and when you go to
claim it, then your claim is
cancelled by telling you different rules and different formalities and you do
not get your claim, so the
biggest thing is that whenever you get your bike
insured, get it
insured from a good trusted company
so that if you have to make a claim later,
your bike gets into an accident
and if you have to make a claim, then
your claim can be passed easily
and your bike can be recovered again
and friends, there are many such things that
when you make a claim in any company, then
many such buttons have to be kept in mind due to
which, that is, if you do
not keep those buttons in mind, if
you do not have that knowledge, then your claim can be
rejected and your
Whatever the total expense of the bike, be it
10000, 15000 or 20000,
that total will have to be paid.
In such a situation, the
insurance company which makes the claim refuses you from the claim, it
clearly denies you.
So friends, suppose your
bike meets with an accident and you go
to the insurance company to claim, then first of all,
wherever your bike meets with an
accident,
immediately videograph it at that very spot,
take some photos of yourself as well. If you have any
injury or anything, then
take photos of yourself as well as the bike. If there is any
person with you,
any other person helping you,
take videography of that as well and
make a group in a proper manner. The
biggest thing is that if
you do not have a valid document like your brother's
RC, if you do not have
insurance, then also
you cannot do anything on this day, whatever your
expenses are.  You may have to provide all that, so
in the document, RC, Insurance,
PUC, if you live in the city, the
argument of PUC is relief,
if you do not have PUC, then also you can have a big
problem. Now friends, there are many such
things that if you or
your brother have an accident, for example,
you are going on the road, suddenly
some animal comes in front of you, you
collide with it and fall down and any accident happens, then
your
claim is passed there normally, if you are
driving a bike after drinking wine, that is, alcohol,
and in such a situation, you have an accident, the
bike gets damaged, and if you have
consumed alcohol there, then also your claim is
not passed, if you were
driving two bikes after drinking alcohol, by doing this the
claim is cancelled there, the
second thing that comes up is that if there are
three people on the bike, three people are
going on the car and suddenly you have an
accident, then in these cases also,
if you are three people on the car and  If you
tell these things there, then
your claim is not passed there also,
there also you may have to bear all the expenses of the accident
and friends, what happens is that if you are
riding a bike, suppose you hit a person
and he suddenly comes out on the road,
even if you have not done this, then
your claim is passed there,
but there are some percentages in that too, that is, the full claim is not passed, it depends on which insurance you have taken, so there are some such
things, some knowledge about it, which
we have to keep
in mind and when we make an insurance claim, then we have to
tell things there in that manner, you have to provide the
complete proof there
and it used to happen on the basis of that proof only, what used to happen earlier, if
you used to make a claim like this earlier, then
your claim would be passed immediately, but now it does
not happen like this, if your bike meets with an
accident, then if you are riding a bike, then
you too must have got some cross eye, so
you too must have medical bills etc. and
many such things  The thing is asked for where
you can get the claim passed. Now friends, let's
talk about when we get the claim passed,
then suppose if you have spent ₹10000 on a bike, then the
claim that will be passed by the company will be
around 767000 only. The second
expense will have to be paid by you.
In the beginning, you will have to pay the entire expense,
then later
when you submit the documents there and it
is verified, on the basis of that, the
amount directly goes into your account,
but 70% or 80% of your claim is
passed,
which we should know because if we do
not know these things and you
go directly to make a claim, then if
you tell everything like this there, you
tell all such things, if you
come in such a fold, then what happens there is that the
insurance people cancel your claim
and mostly the
normal insurance companies, the
local companies, do more
Such companies try to commit fraud and
cancel your claim by doing some trick or the other.
For this, I
told you in the beginning itself that whenever you get
your bike insured, then get it
insured from a trusted insurance company only
so that you do not have to face such problem in future
and your claim can be
passed completely. Friends, it is
very important like suppose
you have an accident and the person in
front dies, then if the person in front of you attacks
you and in
such a situation you do not have the total verified
documents, then you can suffer
huge losses of many types, you can suffer losses of Rs
10 lakh, 5 lakh, 3 lakh, etc.
So whenever you ride a bike, keep the
total documents with you. Get
insurance done from time to time.
Insurance is very important.
If you drive the vehicle without insurance, then
your insurance gets deducted and in such a situation, if an
accident happens, then you may have to
bear a huge loss, so
always keep your bike's insurance
with you.  Keep it in your account and keep renewing it from time to time
because these insurance
documents sometimes
take us to such a place where we have to
regret later that if we had
insurance then we would not have faced such a problem today, so we should
always be clear from our side,
our documents should always be kept
clear and the insurance, the bike
insurance, should always be kept clear
and your insurance should be done from a trusted company only
so that
you can get the claim in future, so friends,
you must have liked today's video, if you
liked it then definitely like the video
and subscribe to the channel so that you keep getting notifications of such
videos and you keep getting Banna Taaro